{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "In the anime ‘Claymore’, who was the most powerful of the ‘Awakened Beings’",
      "options": ["Riful", "Priscilla", "Noel", "Helen"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Vegeta married a sharp-minded scientist. Who was she?",
      "options": ["Android16", "Pam", "Chi-chi", "Bulma"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "As prophesied, Goku transformed into the Super Saiyan form in ‘Dragon Ball Z’. Where did this transformation take place?",
      "options": [
        "Planet Namek",
        "Planet Earth",
        "Planet Arlia",
        "Planet Sadala"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "The Shinigami in love with apples. Can you recall his name",
      "options": ["Ichigo", "Aizen", "Ryuk", "Yamamoto"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is known as the ‘One Punch Man’",
      "options": ["Saitama", "Goku", "Naruto", "Monkey D Luffy"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many Dragon Balls are there?",
      "options": ["Six", "Seven", "Nine", "Twelve"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose body gained the properties of rubber after unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit?",
      "options": [
        "Akagami no Shanks",
        "Buggy",
        "Gol D Roger",
        "Monkey D Luffy"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Who protects the Silver Crystal?",
      "options": ["Silvista", "Crocus", "Sailor Moon", "DoomsDay"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "An outcast prince takes over the revolution by controlling the mind of others. Who is he?",
      "options": [
        "Prince Vegeta",
        "Vinsmoke Sanji",
        "Anos Voldigod",
        "Lelouch Lanperouge."
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you name the director of the ‘Death Note’ 2017 Movie?",
      "options": [
        "Hayao Miyazaki",
        "Makoto Shinkai",
        "Satoshi Kon",
        "Adam Wingard"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Name the voice actor behind the catching pika-pika of Pikachu from ‘Pokemon’.",
      "options": [
        "Yuki Kaji",
        "Christopher Sabat",
        "Ikue Otani",
        "Mamoru Miyano"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "In the anime ‘Hunter X Hunter’, which family is famous for being assassins?",
      "options": [
        "Spiders",
        "Killua’s family",
        "Kufa Vampir",
        "Illumi Zoldyck"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose Zanpakuto is Wabisuke in ‘Bleach’ and had a crush on Hinamori Momo?",
      "options": [
        "Rangiku Matsumoto",
        "Shunsui Kyōraku",
        "Kira Izuru",
        "Byakuya Kuchiki"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Who wrote and illustrated the manga on which ‘One Piece’ is based?",
      "options": [
        "Eiichiro Oda.",
        "Akira Toriyama",
        "Nobuhiro Watsuki",
        "Urasawa Naoki"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first character in ‘Dragon Ball Z’ who achieved the Super Saiyan 2?",
      "options": ["Prince Vegeta", "Trunks", "Goku", "Gohan"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
